thefastmode.com 2015-11-17

# Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Your privacy is important to The Fast Mode.  This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that The Fast Mode collects, and the ways in which The Fast Mode uses that personal information.

**Personal information collection**

The Fast Mode may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * information about your use of this website (including your IP address, your browser type, pages visited, time spent and services/applications accessed and used);
  * information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website (including your personal details, organization and employment details, email and other content addresses, telephone numbers, interests and preferences on the content, enquiries made and services/applications accessed and used);
  * information about transactions carried out over this website (including services and applications used, content downloaded/browsed, orders and purchases made, account numbers, payments made);
  * information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services (including your personal details, organization and employment details, email and other content addresses, telephone numbers, interests and preferences on the content, enquiries made and services/applications accessed and used); and
  * any other information that you send to The Fast Mode.

**Using personal information**

The Fast Mode may use your personal information to:

  * administer this website;
  * personalize the website for you;
  * design new applications and services;
  * create new content;
  * publish user statistics and other aggregate user-related data;
  * enable your access to and use of the website services;
  * publish information about you on the website;
  * send to you products that you purchase;
  * supply to you services that you purchase;
  * send to you statements and invoices;
  * collect payments from you; and
  * send you marketing communications.

Where The Fast Mode discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, The Fast Mode may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

**Securing your data**

The Fast Mode will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

The Fast Mode will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers.

Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be protected by encryption technology.

**Cross-border data transfers**

Information that The Fast Mode collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which The Fast Mode operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

**Updating this statement**

The Fast Mode may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website. 

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes. 

**Other websites**

This website contains links to other websites. 

The Fast Mode is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

_This document was created using a Contractology template available at[http://www.freenetlaw.com](http://www.freenetlaw.com/) under the [Creative Commons Attribution 2.0 UK: England & Wales License](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/2.0/uk/). _
